Meirunas Smitas

meirunas.smi@icloud.com 07727 825042

meru-portfolio.vercel.app

linkedin.com/in/meirunas

Personal Profile

I have gained over 3 years of full-time front-end experience in the pharma agency 28b. I developed multiple web/iOs solutions, internal tools and marketing materials for clients. In other similar roles I used web technologies. Prior to these roles I was studying MSc and BSc Computer Science at London Universities. Over 13 years in the IT environment I built a wide range of skills that could benefit your company.

Key Skills

- Self-motivation and ability to take the initiative
- Team working skills
- Good communication skills
- Able to work well under pressure

Languages: HTML, SCSS, MJML, JavaScript, Handlebars, Typescript

Frameworks & Libraries: Vue.js, React.js, Next.js, Redux

Software: Adobe Cloud, Veeva, Salesforce, npm, MS Office, VS Code, Git, WordPress

Databases: SQL, MySQL, MongoDB

Projects

Portfolio GitHub Personal - Jul 2023 - Now

Building a responsive and dynamic single page application (SPA) portfolio

Global & UK Digital Sales Aid (DSA) GitHub

28b - Dec 2022 - Jun 2023

Involved in creating interactive and static slides. Reviewed Merge Requests by colleagues on 28b & Client Veeva Approved Emails (VAE) Suite Github 28b - Oct - Nov 2022

Implemented different types of email templates serving healthcare purposes

HADEA Website GitHub

HADEA - Aug 2019 - Apr 2020

Created responsive and dynamic charity website

Travel & Explore Now GitLab Final year undergraduate project - Sep 2017 - Jun 2018 Built a full-stack travelling e-commerce website

Work Experience

Targech - Remote Dec 2023 - March 2024 Vue.js Developer

- Analysing existing programs for modification purposes
- Researching and designing new software systems, websites, programs and applications
- Writing and implementing, clean, scalable code
- Troubleshooting and debugging code
- Verifying and deploying software systems
- Evaluating user feedback
- Recommending and executing program improvements
- Creating UI for recruitment website and testing

London

 Configuring and implementing authentication system and payment processing gateway and API

Anglo Skills College - Nottingham IT Administrator

Aug 2023 - Oct 2023

- Procuring, maintaining, and administering computers and office equipment
- Serving as administrator for various corporate software systems
- Deploying and enforcing security policies and procedures
- Providing support and resolving IT-related issues for colleagues
- Updating, improving and developing website using WordPress and Elementor
- Developing and administering Virtual Learning Environment (Moodle)

28b - Huntingdon Junior Developer March 2020 - June 2023

- Investigating and resolving production issues
- Responding to escalated customer questions from the Support team
- Performing root-cause analysis for production errors
- Developing software to automate operational needs
- Implementing Digital Sales Aids for iOS/Web platforms using the Veeva and IQVIA APIs that helped clients with their sales
- Developing responsive emails on CRM, Salesforce and iPad
- Implementing internal tools that helped increase the software quality and accelerated the delivery process
- Using code standard guidelines and best engineering practices, such as code reviews, Git branching strategy and CI/CD
- Improving internal documentation (Company Wiki)

Education & Training

Queen Mary University PGC in Computer Science

2019

University of Westminster BSc Computer Science (1st)

2018

Conel College (Pearson)

2011/2014

BTEC Level 2, 3 and 4 in IT and Computing and Systems Development

Hobbies & Interests

I enjoy travelling and exercising. I like playing games and watching movies.

References

References available on request.